Guide to the Tompkins County Health Services Alliance records, 1975-1977
Tompkins County Health Services Alliance records, 1975-1977
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Tompkins County Health Services Alliance records, 1975-1977.
3883
Tompkins County Health Services Alliance.
1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, memoranda and minutes, reports and surveys.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, memoranda and minutes, reports and surveys of the Tompkins County Health Services Alliance, including material reflecting Cornell University's role in the group.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, memoranda and minutes, reports and surveys of the Tompkins County Health Services Alliance, including material reflecting Cornell University's role in the group.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Tompkins County Health Services Alliance.; Cornell University.
Subjects:
Health planning--New York (State)--Tompkins County.
Places:
Tompkins County (N.Y.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Ad Hoc Committee, Mar. 14, 1976-May 10, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Alliance correspondence and memos, June 5, 1975-June 6, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alliance's Final Report, July 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Alliance's Final Report (original), July 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Alliance's formation and minutes., Mar. 19, 1976-May 10, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Appalachian pre-application (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Consultants (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Data tables (not used in the Final Report) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Draft - Interim Report, Feb. 14, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Executive Committee, June 24, 1976-Apr. 5, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Family Medicine Program survey, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Family Medicine Program survey, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Finance Subcommittee, Sept. 15, 1976-Jan. 22, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Meeting with community physicians, Dec. 13, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Organization Subcommittee, July 20, 1976-Jan. 1, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Original Alliance's committee composition (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Planning and Program Subcommittee, July 19, 1976-Feb. 2, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Primary Care Committee report, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Primary Care report, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Staff minutes, June 23, 1976-May 4, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Steering Committee's Final Report [Cornell U.] (Box 1, Folder 21)